Guide to the Steve Tostenyard collection, 1970-1976 MS 826
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Steve Tostenyard collection
1970-1976
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Tostenyard, Steve
MS 826
2.25 Linear Feet (1 oversize box)
This collections consists of fliers and posters collected by Steve Tostenyard.
Biographical / Historical
Throughout the 1970s, Steve Tostenyard collected posters from music venues and other events in Houston and Austin.
Scope and Contents
This collections consists of fliers and posters collected by Steve Tostenyard.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Accruals
Additional materials are not expected for this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Steve Tostenyard in 2018.
Index Terms
Subjects
Music; Folk-rock music; Art
Subjects (Persons)
Tostenyard, Steve
- Series I: Posters and fliers, 1970-1976
  - Smoke In/Out at Hermann Park, 1970-08-16 (Box 1)
  - "Zacharia" flier, 1971-03-20 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Stills poster, 1971-07-08 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Performers listed include: Stephen Stills, Dallas Taylor, Paul Harris, Calvin "Fozzy" Samuels, The Memphis Horns, Crazy Horse
  - "Rainbow Bridge" viewing at Shamrock Theaters, 1971-08-27-1971-08-29 (Box 1)
  - Traffic, Fairport Convention, The J. Geils Band at the Sam Houston Coliseum, 1971-10-23 (Box 1)
  - Jerry Jeff Walker at Strahan Auditoirum, 1971-10-27 (Box 1)
    Performers listed include: Jerry Jeff Walker, Milton Chesley Carroll, Kinfolk and Friends, Elgin Movement
  - Asleep at the Wheel, Linda Hargrove at La Paloma Theatre, 1972-02-20 (Box 1)
  - It's a Beautiful Day, Seatrain, Lindisfarne at Music Hall, 1972-03-21 (Box 1)
  - Love Street poster, 1972-04-21-1972-04-22 (Box 1)
    Performers listed include: Bloontz All Stars, Carntree, Bargle
  - Jethro Tull at Sam Houston Coliseum, 1972-06-19 (Box 1)
  - It's a Beautiful Day, Wishbone Ash, Argent at Sam Houston Coliseum, 1972-08-17 (Box 1)
  - Headstone, Mike Ericson and Friends at Of Our Own, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Inner Sanctum Records poster, 1972 (Box 1)
  - KAUM 96.5 poster, 1972 (Map-drawer 196, Item 30)
  - The Steve Miller Band at Austin's Municipal Auditorium flier, 1973-10-21 (Box 1)
  - Willie Nelson concert at Hofheinz Pavillion, 1974-06-07 (Box 1)
    Performers listed include: Willie Nelson, Doug Sahm, Billy Joe Shaver, Flyod Tillman, Charlie Harris, Milton Carol, Freda and the Firedogs
  - Willie Nelson and Waylon Jennings at The Summit, 1976-12-31 (Box 1)